BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Memberships and Affiliations, 1945-1968, undated; 4
  - Bishop College-Annual Report (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 239, Folder 10)
  - Bishop College-Financial Report (1 of 3), 1953 (Box 239, Folder 11)
  - Bishop College-Financial Report (2 of 3), 1953 (Box 239, Folder 12)
  - Bishop College-Financial Report (3 of 3), 1953 (Box 239, Folder 13)
  - Bishop College (1 of 6), 1954-1955 (Box 239, Folder 14)
  - Bishop College (2 of 6), 1954-1955 (Box 239, Folder 15)
  - Bishop College (3 of 6), 1954-1955 (Box 239, Folder 16)
  - Bishop College (4 of 6), 1954-1955 (Box 239, Folder 17)
  - Bishop College (5 of 6), 1954-1955 (Box 239, Folder 18)
  - Bishop College (6 of 6), 1954-1955 (Box 239, Folder 19)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (1 of 3), 1955 June 2 (Box 239, Folder 20)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (2 of 3), 1955 June 2 (Box 239, Folder 21)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (3 of 3), 1955 June 2 (Box 239, Folder 22)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President, 1956 May 3 (Box 239, Folder 23)
  - Bishop College-Report of Audit, 1957 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Bishop College (1 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Bishop College (2 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Bishop College (3 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Bishop College-Report to the Special Committee on Finances for Bishop College, 1959 October 28 (Box 240, Folder 5)
  - Bishop College (1 of 6), 1959-1961 (Box 240, Folder 6)
  - Bishop College (2 of 6), 1959-1961 (Box 240, Folder 7)
  - Bishop College (3 of 6), 1959-1961 (Box 240, Folder 8)
  - Bishop College (4 of 6), 1959-1961 (Box 240, Folder 9)
  - Bishop College (5 of 6), 1959-1961 (Box 240, Folder 10)
  - Bishop College (6 of 6), 1959-1961 (Box 240, Folder 11)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 240, Folder 12)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 240, Folder 13)
  - Bishop College-Financial Statements and Report of the President (1 of 2), 1961 May-September (Box 240, Folder 14)
  - Bishop College-Financial Statements and Report of the President (2 of 2), 1961 May-September (Box 240, Folder 15)
  - Bishop College (1 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 240, Folder 16)
  - Bishop College (2 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 240, Folder 17)
  - Bishop College (3 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 240, Folder 18)
  - Bishop College (1 of 4), 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 19)
  - Bishop College (2 of 4), 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 20)
  - Bishop College (3 of 4), 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 21)
  - Bishop College (4 of 4), 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 22)
  - Bishop College-Profile of Bishop College 1954-1974 Submitted on January 13, 1964 to the Ford Foundation (1 of 3), 1964 January 13 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Bishop College-Profile of Bishop College 1954-1974 Submitted on January 13, 1964 to the Ford Foundation (2 of 3), 1964 January 13 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Bishop College-Profile of Bishop College 1954-1974 Submitted on January 13, 1964 to the Ford Foundation (3 of 3), 1964 January 13 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Bishop College-Report (1 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Bishop College-Report (2 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Bishop College-Report (3 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Bishop College-Report (4 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Bishop College-Report (5 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 8)
  - Bishop College-Report (6 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 9)
  - Bishop College-Report (7 of 7), 1964 (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - Bishop College-Report (1 of 4), 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 11)
  - Bishop College-Report (2 of 4), 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 12)
  - Bishop College-Report (3 of 4), 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 13)
  - Bishop College-Report (4 of 4), 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 14)
  - Bishop College (1 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 241, Folder 15)
  - Bishop College (2 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 241, Folder 16)
  - Bishop College (3 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 241, Folder 17)
  - Bishop College (4 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 241, Folder 18)
  - Bishop College (5 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Bishop College (6 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Bishop College (7 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Bishop College (8 of 8), 1969-1977 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Bishop College-School Year Activity Calendar, 1969-1970 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Bishop College-General File (1 of 4), 1971-1976 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - Bishop College-General File (2 of 4), 1971-1976 (Box 242, Folder 7)
  - Bishop College-General File (3 of 4), 1971-1976 (Box 242, Folder 8)
  - Bishop College-General File (4 of 4), 1971-1976 (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President to the Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Downtown YMCA, Dallas (1 of 2), 1959 October 21 (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Bishop College-Report of the President to the Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Downtown YMCA, Dallas (2 of 2), 1959 October 21 (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Bishop College-Bishop Butler Merger, undated (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - Botthof School of Media (1 of 2), undated (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Botthof School of Media (2 of 2), undated (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 3), 1953 (Box 242, Folder 15)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 3), 1953 (Box 242, Folder 16)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 3), 1953 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - Boy Scouts (4 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - Boy Scouts (5 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Boy Scouts (6 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scouts (7 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 11)
  - Boy Scouts (8 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts (9 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 13)
  - Boy Scouts (10 of 10), 1955-1956 (Box 243, Folder 14)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 4), 1956-1957 (Box 243, Folder 15)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 4), 1956-1957 (Box 243, Folder 16)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 4), 1956-1957 (Box 243, Folder 17)
  - Boy Scouts (4 of 4), 1956-1957 (Box 243, Folder 18)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 5), 1957-1958 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 5), 1957-1958 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 5), 1957-1958 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts (4 of 5), 1957-1958 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scouts (5 of 5), 1957-1958 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Boy Scouts (4 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Boy Scouts (5 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scouts (6 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Boy Scouts (7 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts (8 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 13)
  - Boy Scouts (9 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 14)
  - Boy Scouts (10 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 15)
  - Boy Scouts (11 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 16)
  - Boy Scouts (12 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 17)
  - Boy Scouts (13 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 18)
  - Boy Scouts (14 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 19)
  - Boy Scouts (15 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 20)
  - Boy Scouts (16 of 16), 1958-1959 (Box 244, Folder 21)
  - Boy Scouts (1 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts (2 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts (3 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts (4 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scouts (5 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts (6 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts (7 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Boy Scouts (8 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Boy Scouts (9 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Boy Scouts (10 of 10), 1959-1960 (Box 245, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (1 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 11)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (2 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (3 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 13)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (4 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 14)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (5 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 15)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (6 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 16)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (7 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 17)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (8 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 18)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (9 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 19)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (10 of 15), 1960 (Box 245, Folder 20)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (11 of 15), 1960 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (12 of 15), 1960 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (13 of 15), 1960 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (14 of 15), 1960 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (15 of 15), 1960 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scouts-Scouting, 1962 February (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (1 of 3), 1967-1976 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (2 of 3), 1967-1976 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Boy Scouts-Reports (3 of 3), 1967-1976 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Boy Scouts-Scout Study Committee (1 of 4), 1966 (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scouts-Scout Study Committee (2 of 4), 1966 (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - Boy Scouts-Scout Study Committee (3 of 4), 1966 (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts-Scout Study Committee (4 of 4), 1966 (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Boy Scouts-God and Country Medal with Case (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - Brotherhood, 1960-1961 (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - Bulletins, 1963, 1965-1967 (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (1 of 10), undated (Box 246, Folder 17)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (2 of 10), undated (Box 246, Folder 18)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (3 of 10), undated (Box 246, Folder 19)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (4 of 10), undated (Box 246, Folder 20)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (5 of 10), undated (Box 246, Folder 21)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (6 of 10), undated (Box 246, Folder 22)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (7 of 10), undated (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (8 of 10), undated (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (9 of 10), undated (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 1 (10 of 10), undated (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 2 (1 of 6), undated (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 2 (2 of 6), undated (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 2 (3 of 6), undated (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 2 (4 of 6), undated (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 2 (5 of 6), undated (Box 247, Folder 9)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ-Ten Basic Steps Towards Christian Maturity 2 (6 of 6), undated (Box 247, Folder 10)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (1 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 247, Folder 11)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (2 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 247, Folder 12)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (3 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 247, Folder 13)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (4 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 247, Folder 14)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (5 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 247, Folder 15)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 247, Folder 16)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 247, Folder 17)
  - Christian Children’s Fund, 1958 (Box 247, Folder 18)
  - Christian Children’s Fund, 1960 (Box 247, Folder 19)
  - Christian Citizen (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 247, Folder 20)
  - Christian Citizen (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 247, Folder 21)
  - Christian Citizens in Government (1 of 2), 1963 September 13 (Box 247, Folder 22)
  - Christian Citizens in Government (2 of 2), 1963 September 13 (Box 247, Folder 23)
  - Christian Citizenship, 1961-1962 (Box 247, Folder 24)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (1 of 5), 1953 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (2 of 5), 1953 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (3 of 5), 1953 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (4 of 5), 1953 (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (5 of 5), 1953 (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (1 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (2 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Christian Education Commission-Harold Haswell (3 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Christian Education Commission-Report of Dallas Conference Concerning Possibilities for New Baptist Educational Institutions, 1956 December 21 (Box 248, Folder 11)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 12)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 13)
  - Christian Education Commission (3 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 14)
  - Christian Education Commission (4 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 15)
  - Christian Education Commission (5 of 5), 1956-1957 (Box 248, Folder 16)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1957-1959 (Box 248, Folder 17)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 248, Folder 18)
  - Christian Education Commission-Texas, 1959-1961 (Box 248, Folder 19)
  - Christian Education Commission-Charles Welborn Speech on Bible Requirement, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 20)
  - Christian Life Commission-A.C. Miller, 1951 (Box 248, Folder 21)
  - Christian Life Commission-A.C. Miller (1 of 2), 1952 (Box 248, Folder 22)
  - Christian Life Commission-A.C. Miller (2 of 2), 1952 (Box 248, Folder 23)
  - Christian Maturity Council, 1962-1963 (Box 248, Folder 24)
  - Christian Maturity Council, 1965-1967 (Box 248, Folder 25)
  - Club Dues and Expenses, 1960-1964 (Box 248, Folder 26)
  - Civil Rights Commission (1 of 3), 1958 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights Commission (2 of 3), 1958 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights Commission (3 of 3), 1958 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Civil Rights (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Civil Rights (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 249, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Civil Rights, 1959-1960 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Civil Rights-State Advisory Committees Directory (1 of 2), 1959 May 1 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Civil Rights-State Advisory Committees Directory (2 of 2), 1959 May 1 (Box 249, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Civil Rights, 1960-1961 (Box 249, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1959 (Box 249, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Higher Education (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 249, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Higher Education (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 249, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Higher Education (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 249, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Higher Education (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 249, Folder 14)
  - Commissions Mixed, 1961-1962 (Box 249, Folder 15)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1952 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - The Committee of the Governing Boards of State Colleges and Universities (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - The Committee of the Governing Boards of State Colleges and Universities (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - The Committee of the Governing Boards of State Colleges and Universities, 1961 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Committees Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 250, Folder 5)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 250, Folder 6)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 250, Folder 7)
  - Cooper Foundation Report, 1958-1959 (Box 250, Folder 8)
  - Cooper Foundation Report, 1970-1971 (Box 250, Folder 9)
  - Corporate Aid to College, 1953 (Box 250, Folder 10)
  - Corpus Christi University (1 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 11)
  - Corpus Christi University (2 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 12)
  - Corpus Christi University (3 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 13)
  - Corpus Christi University (4 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 14)
  - Corpus Christi University (5 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 15)
  - Corpus Christi University (6 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 16)
  - Corpus Christi University (7 of 7), 1948-1950 (Box 250, Folder 17)
  - Cotton Bowl Athletic Association, 1950-1951 (Box 250, Folder 18)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education, 1953 (Box 250, Folder 19)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education (1 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 250, Folder 20)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education (2 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 250, Folder 21)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education (3 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 250, Folder 22)
  - Councils Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 250, Folder 23)
  - Crusaders Against Delinquency, 1956-1957 (Box 250, Folder 24)
  - Crusaders Against Delinquency (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 250, Folder 25)
  - Crusaders Against Delinquency (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 250, Folder 26)
  - Crusaders Against Delinquency, 1961, 1964, 1966 (Box 250, Folder 27)
  - Dallas Council on World Affairs, 1962 (Box 250, Folder 28)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1960 (Box 250, Folder 29)
  - Department of Health Education and Welfare, 1957 (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - Department of Health Education and Welfare, 1959-1960 (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Development Council, undated (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Development Council Mailing List, undated (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - East Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1949-1951 (Box 251, Folder 5)
  - Education Commission-(Southern), 1961 (Box 251, Folder 6)
  - Education Commission-Texas (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 251, Folder 7)
  - Education Commission-Texas (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 251, Folder 8)
  - Endowment Highlights, 1958 (Box 251, Folder 9)
  - Ex-Students-Birth Announcements (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 251, Folder 10)
  - Ex-Students-Birth Announcements (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 251, Folder 11)
  - Ex-Students Association, 1961 (Box 251, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, 1960 (Box 251, Folder 13)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1961 (Box 251, Folder 14)
  - Federal Security Agency-Office of Education, 1950-1951 (Box 251, Folder 15)
  - First Baptist Church-Austin, 1949 (Box 251, Folder 16)
  - First Baptist Church-Dallas, 1962 (Box 251, Folder 17)
  - First Baptist Church-Dallas Executive Board, 1962-1963 (Box 251, Folder 18)
  - First Baptist Church-Million Dollar Campaign, 1957 (Box 251, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation, 1952 (Box 251, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation, 1953 (Box 251, Folder 21)
  - Ford Foundation (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 251, Folder 22)
  - Ford Foundation (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation, 1957 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation-News from the Ford Foundation, 1959 July (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation, 1961-1962 (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Mission Board, 1960 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Service Program, 1956-1957 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Foundation for Religious Action in the Social and Civil Order, 1959 (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - Freedom in Action, 1961 (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - Freedoms Foundation Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge-1961 Awards Juror’s Book (Box 252, Folder 11)
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge-Judging Procedure and General Information, 1962 (Box 252, Folder 12)
  - Funds, Mixed, 1962 (Box 252, Folder 13)
  - General Boards, 1962 (Box 252, Folder 14)
  - General Organizations, undated (Box 285 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Gifts and Donations, 1963-1964 (Box 252, Folder 15)
  - Golden Gate Baptist Theological Seminary-Academic Session, 1962-1963 (Box 252, Folder 16)
  - Greater Waco Safety Council, 1960 (Box 252, Folder 17)
  - Hardin-Simmons University, 1950 (Box 252, Folder 18)
  - Higher Education, 1960 (Box 252, Folder 19)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1960 (Box 252, Folder 20)
  - Higher Education Bulletin (1 of 3), 1960-1961 (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Higher Education Bulletin (2 of 3), 1960-1961 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education Bulletin (3 of 3), 1960-1961 (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education Bulletin, 1961-1962 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Howard Payne College (1 of 3), 1949-1950 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Howard Payne College (2 of 3), 1949-1950 (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Howard Payne College (3 of 3), 1949-1950 (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Howard Payne College, 1951 (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Human Events, 1959 (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Human Relations Council, 1951 (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - Independence Association, 1968-1969 (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - Independent College Funds of America, 1960 (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - Institutions (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 253, Folder 13)
  - Institutions (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - Institutions Mixed, 1962 (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - Institute of International Education-Meeting of College and University Representatives, 1965 April 23-24 (Box 253, Folder 16)
  - International Cooperation Administration 1957 and 1959 (1 of 2), 1957, 1959 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - International Cooperation Administration 1957 and 1959 (2 of 2), 1957, 1959 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Israel-American Institute of Biblical Studies-Christian News from Israel, 1961 May (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Its Smarter Not to Drink, undated (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - John Price Jones Company, 1960-1962 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - John Price Jones Company, 1960-1961 (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - Kiplinger, 1958-1959 (Box 254, Folder 7)
  - KWBU Radio Station, 1950-1951 (Box 254, Folder 8)
  - KWBU Radio Station (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 254, Folder 9)
  - KWBU Radio Station (2 of 3), 1951 (Box 254, Folder 10)
  - KWBU Radio Station (3 of 3), 1951 (Box 254, Folder 11)
  - KWBU Radio Station (1 of 4), 1952 (Box 254, Folder 12)
  - KWBU Radio Station (2 of 4), 1952 (Box 254, Folder 13)
  - KWBU Radio Station (3 of 4), 1952 (Box 254, Folder 14)
  - KWBU Radio Station (4 of 4), 1952 (Box 254, Folder 15)
  - KWBU Radio Station (1 of 3), 1953 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - KWBU Radio Station (2 of 3), 1953 (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - KWBU Radio Station (3 of 3), 1953 (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - KWBU Radio Station (1 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - KWBU Radio Station (2 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - KWBU Radio Station (3 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - KWBU Radio Station (4 of 4), 1954-1955 (Box 255, Folder 7)
  - KWBU Radio Station (1 of 6), 1955-1956 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  - KWBU Radio Station (2 of 6), 1955-1956 (Box 256, Folder 2)
  - KWBU Radio Station (3 of 6), 1955-1956 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - KWBU Radio Station (4 of 6), 1955-1956 (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - KWBU Radio Station (5 of 6), 1955-1956 (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - KWBU Radio Station (6 of 6), 1955-1956 (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - KWBU Radio Station, 1956 (Box 256, Folder 7)
  - KWBU Television, 1953 (Box 256, Folder 8)
  - Life Line, 1959-1960 (Box 256, Folder 9)
  - Life Line, 1960 (Box 256, Folder 10)
  - Life Line-Radio Transcript, 1961 July 15 (Box 256, Folder 11)
  - The Logos Corporation (1 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - The Logos Corporation (2 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - March of Dimes, 1963 (Box 257, Folder 3)